I identified Master as the Blue Ghost.
Aku mengidentifikasi guruku adalah hantu biru.
How could I possibly identify Master as the Blue Ghost?
Bagaimana aku bisa menuduh guruku sebagai hantu biru?
That's not right.
Tidak.
I didn't see Master yesterday.
Aku belum bertemu Guru kemarin.
What's your last memory then?
Di mana ingatan terakhirmu?
Yesterday,
Kemarin...
after senior brother went upstairs.
Setelah Senior naik ke atas,
Brother Feng came shortly after.
Kak Feng akan segera datang.
He said
Dia bilang
he needed to talk to me about something.
dia ada urusan mencariku.
Then he pulled me
Lalu menarikku
to the side.
ke samping.
And then,
Lalu...
I don't remember anything after that.
aku tidak ingat.
He came yesterday with people from the Imperial Guard,
Kemarin dia membawa orang dari Kementerian Keamanan
just to arrest Master.
untuk menangkap Guru.
He was convinced that Master is the Blue Ghost.
Dia yakin bahwa Guru adalah Hantu Hijau.
This matter
Masalah ini
is related to Brother Feng.
berhubungan dengan Kakak Feng.
But he's your own brother.
Namun, dia adalah kakak kandungmu.
That doesn't stop him from hiding things from me.
Itu juga tidak menghalangi dia menyembunyikannya dariku.
After all, he's kept secrets from me before.
Bagaimanapun, dia sudah pernah menyembunyikannya sekali.
Junior sister,
Adik.
we'll see each other again soon.
Kita akan segera bertemu lagi.
How could this happen?
Bagaimana ini bisa terjadi?
My mother is not the Blue Demon.
Ibuku bukan hantu hijau.
She can't be the Blue Demon.
Dia tidak mungkin adalah hantu hijau.
My mother...
Ibuku...
She's not the Blue Demon, right?
Dia bukan hantu hijau, 'kan?
She's not.
Dia bukan.
You're back.
Sudah pulang?
Mm-hmm.
Ya.
Come in.
Masuklah.
How is General He?
Bagaimana keadaan Jenderal He?
Hong Guo, tell me the truth.
Buah merah, jujurlah padaku.
Our benefactor, he...
Sang penyelamat...
He's severely injured.
terluka parah.
If we can't find a way to save him,
Jika tidak menemukan cara untuk menyelamatkannya,
he might not make it through the night.
dia tidak akan bertahan malam ini.
It's all my fault.
Ini semua salahku.
He doesn't blame you.
Dia tidak menyalahkanmu.
He said,
Dia bilang,
if he had told you the truth earlier,
jika aku memberitahumu kebenarannya lebih awal,
you wouldn't have been driven to desperation
kau tak akan putus asa
and learned the Nightmare Palm technique.
untuk berlatih Tapak Mimpi.
He's a good man.
Dia orang yang baik.
But I've taken the wrong path.
Tapi aku salah jalan.
There's no turning back for me now.
Aku tidak bisa kembali lagi.
This is the only way.
Hanya bisa begini.
Hong Guo.
Buah merah.
I said a lot of hurtful things to you before.
Aku mengatakan banyak hal buruk kepadamu.
I even wanted to end our sisterhood.
dan memutuskan hubungan persaudaraan denganmu.
It was all my fault.
Ini semua salahku.
If you want to hit me or scold me,
Jika kamu ingin memukulku, memarahiku,
I'll take it all.
aku akan menerimanya.
But Hong Guo,
Tapi kacang merah,
can you please not leave me?
bisakah kamu jangan meninggalkanku?
You're the only family I have left.
Aku hanya punya kau sebagai keluargaku.
How could you think that?
Kenapa kau berpikir begitu?
If anyone's at fault,
Jika salah,
it's me for keeping secrets from you.
akulah yang menyembunyikannya darimu terlebih dahulu.
Don't worry.
Jangan khawatir.
I'll stick with you for life.
Aku akan bergantung padamu seumur hidup.
If I left the teahouse,
Jika aku meninggalkan kedai teh,
eating, drinking, and everything else
makan, minum, buang air,
would cost money.
semuanya butuh uang.
As someone who loves money so much,
Aku begitu suka uang,
how could I possibly take such a loss?
bagaimana mungkin rugi seperti ini?
Indeed.
Benar.
Oh, right.
Omong-omong,
Do you still have that paperweight?
apakah kamu masih punya kertas itu?
It's still with me.
Masih ada padaku.
Brother Feng didn't take it.
Kakak Feng tidak mengambilnya.
That's great!
Bagus sekali.
Our benefactor can be saved now.
Sang penyelamat bisa diselamatkan.
Yun'er,
Kak Yun'er.
take the paperweight.
Kamu bawa tisu.
I'll go prepare the car.
Aku pergi siapkan mobil.
We'll go rescue General He together.
Kita selamatkan Jenderal He bersama.
Alright.
Baik.
How do you feel?
Bagaimana perasaanmu?
About what I told you,
[Hati-hati]
you must be careful.
harus hati-hati.
Keep a close eye on Feng Chen.
Awasi Feng Chen.
If there's any sign of trouble,
Jika terjadi sesuatu,
tell me immediately.
segera beri tahu aku.
Don't worry, senior brother.
Kakak tenang saja.
It concerns our master's safety.
Ini menyangkut keselamatan Guru.
I won't take it lightly.
Aku tidak bisa main-main.
Senior brother,
Senior.
what do you plan to do next?
Apa rencanamu selanjutnya?
Go to the cave in West Mountain.
Pergi ke Gua Xishan.
Hurry!
Cepat!
Benefactor.
Sang penyelamat.
General He.
Jenderal He.
Junior sister.
Adik seperguruan.
Why are you here?
Kenapa kamu datang?
General He.
Jenderal He.
I am Yun'er.
Aku Yun'er.
The daughter of Si Tu Wan Nan.
Putri Situ Feinan.
Junior sister.
Adik Seperguruan.
I've let you down.
Aku bersalah padamu.
I couldn't stop Yun'er.
Tidak bisa menghentikan Yun'er.
General He.
Jenderal He.
I've brought the paperweight.
Aku membawa kertas polisinya.
Hong Guo said.
Buah merah bilang,
Do you have a way to counter this Soul-Crushing Palm?
kau punya cara untuk melepaskan Tapak Penghancur Mimpi?
We should act without delay.
Jangan ditunda lagi.
Let's try it quickly.
Ayo kita coba.
What's wrong?
Ada apa?
The paperweight you brought
Kertas yang kau bawa
is a fake.
adalah barang palsu.
That's impossible.
Tak mungkin.
This paperweight was given to me by Feng Chen.
Feng Chen yang memberiku kertas ini.
Could it be that
Jangan-jangan...
he has been deceiving me all along?
dia terus membohongiku?
Feng Chen is a man of deep schemes.
Feng Chen sangat licik.
He's also obsessed with power plays.
dan suka menggunakan kekuasaan.
His eagerness to pin the Blue Ghost's crimes on me this time
Kali ini dia buru-buru menuduhku atas kejahatan hantu hijau.
is certainly not as simple as avenging his father.
bukan hanya untuk membalaskan dendam ayahnya.
From now on,
Mulai sekarang,
stay away from him.
menjauhlah darinya.
Don't let yourself be harmed by him.
Jangan dicelakai olehnya.
Yi Chu Pin Yi
Satu, satu.
Beijing National Fashion Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
PT. Media Budaya Fengshang nasional Beijing.
Horgos Daobo Spring Film and Television Culture Media Co., Ltd.
PT. Perusahaan Budaya dan Film Musim Semi HolGuo.
- Production -
Produksi.
- Art Director -
[Bimbingan seni]
You Jianming
You Jianming.
- Cast -
Arloji aktor.
- Filming Crew -
[Staf syuting]
White Dot Pictures
White Media.
Visual Effects Production
Produksi efek visual.
Music Production
Produksi musik.
Beijing Landuo Music
Beijing Randao Music.
Chizhou Haochen Culture Media Co., Ltd.
PT. Media Haochen dari Chizhou.